<?xml version='1.0'?>
<doc>
    <character id="mob" order="0">
        <name>Shigeo Kageyama</name>
        <shortName>MOB</shortName>
        <description>An 8th grader known as “MOB”. He has psychic powers strong enough to destroy an organization known
            as “Claw” with world domination in mind. He is not much of a talker and cannot blend in with the crowd.
            Looks up to Reigen as his “Master” since he advised him on how to treat his dangerous psychic powers. Since
            then, he has been worshiped as the leader of cult religious group known as “Psycho Helmet” and being feared
            by the local delinquent as “White-T Poison”. However, he doesn’t mind anything at all.
        </description>
        <icon>img/chara_icons/mob.png</icon>
        <image>img/characters/mob.png</image>
    </character>
    <character id="reigen" order="1">
        <name>Reigen Arataka</name>
        <shortName>REIGEN</shortName>
        <description>Self-proclaimed psychic who owns a psychic counselling shop known as “Sporit and Such”.
            However his real talent lies in the art of conversation as he has no actual psychic powers. When things are
            too much for him to handle, he calls his assistant, MOB to deal with it. He also watches over MOB and
            support him mentally. He can now see higher evil-spirit Ekubo after the incident with the seventh division
            of the “Claw”.
        </description>
        <icon>img/chara_icons/reigen.png</icon>
        <image>img/characters/reigen.png</image>
    </character>
    <character id="ekubo" order="2">
        <name>Ekubo</name>
        <shortName>EKUBO</shortName>
        <description>A higher evil-spirit who had the ambition on becoming God. He can take over the bodies of people
            and move them accordingly. He met MOB when he set up a dubious religious cult called “LOL”. Since then, he
            believes that MOB is the true God material and spends time with him ever since. Even though he is after MOB
            and his immense powers, he tends to lend a hand to him when he needs. Although he tries to be evil, he is
            good in general.
        </description>
        <icon>img/chara_icons/ekubo.png</icon>
        <image>img/characters/ekubo.png</image>
    </character>
    <character id="ritsu" order="3">
        <name>Ritsu Kageyama</name>
        <shortName>RITSU</shortName>
        <description>MOB’s younger brother who is in the school council and good in both school and sports. He is also
            sociable, which is the opposite of MOB. He always feared and envied his brother since he witnessed MOB’s
            power getting out of control, His psychic powers were awoken by the “School Reform” incident conducted by
            student council president, Kamuro. As MOB is somewhat naïve, he supports him closely.
        </description>
        <icon>img/chara_icons/ritsu.png</icon>
        <image>img/characters/ritsu.png</image>
    </character>
    <character id="teru" order="4">
        <name>Teruki Hanazawa</name>
        <shortName>TERU</shortName>
        <description>He is another psychic, whom once stood before MOB as the delinquent leader of Black-Vinegar Junior
            High. However, he has the tendency to become pigeon legged when he uses his powers. He has grown mentally
            since the battle with MOB and when Ritsu is taken by the seventh division, he accompanied MOB to rescue him.
            They both fought fierce battles with the high ranked members. He is now a loyal friend and has healthy
            rivalry with MOB. His nickname is “Teru”.
        </description>
        <icon>img/chara_icons/teru.png</icon>
        <image>img/characters/teru.png</image>
    </character>
    <character id="tsubomi" order="5">
        <name>Tsubomi</name>
        <shortName>TSUBOMI</shortName>
        <description>MOB’s childhood friend, who he has a crush on, She is adored by her school friends for her charming
            looks. Mob has joined Body Improvement Club in order for her to like him. Tempted by Mezato, Mob even tries
            for the school student presidency! Does she know how much effort he puts in to be perfect for her?
        </description>
        <icon>img/chara_icons/tsubomi.png</icon>
        <image>img/characters/tsubomi.png</image>
    </character>
    <character id="shou" order="6">
        <name>Shou Suzuki</name>
        <shortName>SHOU</shortName>
        <description>A mysterious boy whom Ritsu met when he was abducted by the seventh division of the “Claw”. His
            ostensible purpose was to participate in a training session but his real purpose was to head hunt for his
            team. He had been interested in MOB and Ritsu from early one. He is also a powerful psychic himself.
        </description>
        <icon>img/chara_icons/shou.png</icon>
        <image>img/characters/shou.png</image>
    </character>
    <character id="mezato" order="7">
        <name>Ichi Mezato</name>
        <shortName>MEZATO</shortName>
        <description>She is the member of the school news club. She is always looking for a big news with her camera
            around her neck. She first met MOB when she attended the cult religion “LOL” meeting undercover. She notices
            his psychic powers and been trying to expose his secret ever since. She has persuaded MOB to compete for the
            school student presidency, however…
        </description>
        <icon>img/chara_icons/mezato.png</icon>
        <image>img/characters/mezato.png</image>
    </character>

</doc>